{
    "easy":{
        "questions":[
            {
                "ID": 1,
                "question": "4 x 4",
                "correctAnswer": 16
            },
            {
                "ID": 2,
                "question": "5 - 2",
                "correctAnswer": 3
            },
            {
                "ID": 3,
                "question": "25 + 15",
                "correctAnswer": 40
            },
            {
                "ID": 4,
                "question": "35 + 25",
                "correctAnswer": 60
            },
            {
                "ID": 5,
                "question": "25 + 15",
                "correctAnswer": 40
            },
            {
                "ID": 6,
                "question": "51 + 16",
                "correctAnswer": 67
            },
            {
                "ID": 7,
                "question": "48 + 42",
                "correctAnswer": 90
            },
            {
                "ID": 8,
                "question": "47 + 39",
                "correctAnswer": 86
            },
            {
                "ID": 9,
                "question": "3 x 9",
                "correctAnswer": 27
            },
            {
                "ID": 10,
                "question": "20 - 13",
                "correctAnswer": 7
            }
        ]
    },

    "normal":{
        "questions":[
            {
                "ID": 1,
                "question": "32 x 3",
                "correctAnswer": 96
            },
            {
                "ID": 2,
                "question": "36 / 6",
                "correctAnswer": 6
            }
        ]
    },

    "hard":{
        "questions":[
            {
                "ID": 1,
                "question": "sqrt(9)",
                "correctAnswer": 3
            },
            {
                "ID": 2,
                "question": "12 x 12",
                "correctAnswer": 144
            }
        ]
    }
}